http://www.benedictine.edu/about/policies/privacy

About
Mission & Values Heritage Benedictine 2020 Traditions Board of Directors Lists & Rankings Accreditation Campus Buildings & Locations Facilities
Give
benedictine.edu Privacy PolicyUpdated February 12, 2018This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their information is being used on the Benedictine College main web site (https://www.benedictine.edu). By using this website, you consent to the privacy practices described in this policy.What is personally identifiable information?Personally identifiable information, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. It includes:A first and last nameA home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or townAn email addressA telephone numberA social security numberCollection of personally identifiable informationBenedictine College does not automatically collect personally identifiable information about visitors to the benedictine.edu web site.Benedictine College may use online forms to collect personally identifiable information, including your name and contact information (email, address, telephone number) and other identifiers in order to allow you to submit questions and comments, register for events, or sign up for email newsletters.How do we use personally identifiable information?We may use the personal information we collect from you when you register for an event, sign up for a newsletter, apply to the college, or use other site features in the following ways:To contact with you within the context in which you provided the information. For example, sending you an email reminder that the event you registered for takes place in two weeks.To reach out to you with additional communication based on the personal details and interests you sent to us. For example, if you attended an annual event one year, we may send you a promotional postcard for the event the following year.At any time, you may opt out of receiving further communications from Benedictine College, such as email and physical mail. However, you may not opt out of receiving simple responses to your use of site features, such as confirmation emails for web form submissions.We will not reveal personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties unless the following conditions apply:We have your consent to share the information.We are sharing such information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes.Other conditions as described in this Privacy Policy.We may share information that does not personally identify you without restriction.Other information we collectBenedictine College, like most institutions and organizations on the Internet, tracks web browsing patterns to better understand how the college website is being used and for other purposes. Generic information is collected through the use of “cookies,” which are small text files placed on your computer through your web browser.You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, doing so may prevent you from using the benedictine.edu website to the fullest.Google AnalyticsThe benedictine.edu website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use our sites. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website includes your IP address. This information is sent to Google and stored on Google's servers. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity, and providing other web-related analysis. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.You may opt-out of Google Analytics tracking though the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. Please visit the following pages for more information on Google Analytics terms of use, Google’s privacy practices, and Google Analytics privacy document.Facebook PixelThe benedictine.edu website uses Facebook Pixel, from Facebook, Inc., to track visits to the website from users who clicked on Facebook ads. We use this information to determine the effectiveness of our advertisements on the Facebook social media platform.Other Tracking ServicesThe benedictine.edu website may use outside advertising agencies to track specific user behavior and visits to specific web pages. We use this information to deliver digital advertisements in the future to visitors whose past site usage suggests certain interests.  External linksThe benedictine.edu site may embed or provide links to external websites not owned by, or officially affiliated with, Benedictine College. Benedictine College is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.Changes to this policyBenedictine College reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. If we make changes we will note the date the updates were added to the policy at the top of this page. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to this privacy policy.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.Benedictine College benedictine.edu 1020 N. Second St. Atchison, Kansas 66002 United States of America webmaster@benedictine.edu 913-360-7355
